    "category": "adventure",
    "category": "sports",
    "category": "action",
    "category": "action",
    "category": "adventure",
    "category": "shooting",
    "category": "sports",
    "category": "multiplayer",
    "category": "multiplayer",
    "category": "racing",
    "category": "racing",
    "category": "racing",
    "category": "io",
  "category": "card",
  "category": "beauty",
  "category": "racing",
  "category": "racing",
  "category": "escape",
  "category": "puzzle",
  "description": "8-Ball Billiards is a free online pool game in our sports category ideal for one or two players. You can play solo against AI or challenge other players in two-player mode. The game is easy for anyone to play, so pick up a cue and line up your first shot.\n\nHow to Play 8 Ball Billiards Classic\n8 Ball Billiards Classic is much like the classic in-person game -- your goal is to pocket all your balls (either solids or stripes) and sink the 8-ball to win. Use your mouse to aim the cue stick and adjust the power of your shot. Click and drag the cue stick back to set your shot鈥檚 power, then release it to strike the cue ball. This is a 2-player game, so carefully plan each shot to outmaneuver whoever you're playing with and clear the table before they do!\n\nPick a ball\n8-Ball Billiards is an intuitive billiards game where you must pot all striped or spotted balls, depending on what you're assigned to. The balls you鈥檙e assigned depend on what ball is potted first so shoot for the win!\n\nLine up your cue\nThe controls are easy. Simply click and drag to find the right level of force, then line up the angle with the ball that seems easiest to pot next. Remember that this is pool, so save the 8-ball until you have potted all your balls鈥攐therwise, you will lose!\n\nFeatures\nEasy and intuitive controls\nPlay against the computer or a friend\nKeep track of your stats\nSmooth graphics and animations\nSave your in-game progress to your CrazyGames account",
  "category": "pool",
  "category": "shooting",
  "category": "driving",
  "category": "clicker",
  "category": "strategy",
  "category": "racing",
  "category": "minecraft",
  "category": "beauty",
  "category": "racing",
  "category": "racing",
  "category": "racing",
